Guide to the Rice University Campus Photographer Files, 1970-2004 UA 188
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Addenda, transferred in 2011, 115370
  - Subseries B: Events, 115520
    - Leebron, President-Elect press conference, December 17, 2004; 116756 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Lord Sainsbury, 2002; 116431 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Lunar New Year, 116432 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Luncheons, dinners, and cocktail parties, 116433 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - March of Dimes, 1995; 116434 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Matriculation/O Week, 1991-1995, undated; 116435 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Matriculation/O Week, 1996; 116436 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Matriculation/O Week, 1997; 117527 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Matriculation/O Week, 1998; 117528 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Matriculation/O Week, 2000; 117529 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Matriculation/O Week, 2001; 117530 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Matriculation/O Week, 2002; 118056 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Matriculation/O Week, 2003; 117563 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Matriculation/O Week, 2004; 117540 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - May Fete, 117459 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Mini Maestro, 117428 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Multicultural, 116437 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Nano Day, 116438 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Nobel Prize, 116440 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Olympic Torch Run, 2001; 116441 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Open House - Martel/Jones, 117456 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Outreach Day, September 24, 1994; 116442 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Outreach Day, 1998; 116443 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Owl Day, 1994, 2000; 116444 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Owl Weekend, 1998; 118756 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Parents Weekend, 1999; 117426 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Parents Weekend, 2000; 117455 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Parents Weekend, 2003; 117427 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Pow Wow, 116687 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - President's Lecture Series, 116448 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - President's Report, 116449 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - R Awards, 116450 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Rayzor Lecture - President Hackerman and Glenn T. Seaborg, November 16, 1982; 116581 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Reforestation Program - Louisiana, 117458 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Retirement - Facilities, 116582 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Retirement - Marion Hicks, 116451 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Retirement - Carl McDowell, 116452 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Retirement - Shirley Redwine, 116583 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - RSVP, 116454 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Scholarship - James L. Byrd, 116455 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Service Awards, 116456 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Shell Conference, 116457 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Shepherd School, 117543 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Shepherd School Opera, 117524 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Shepherd School with elementary school students, 117429 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Students - demonstrations/vigils, 116458 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Students - formals, 116459 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Summit of the Mind, 1998; 116460 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Texas State Senate Hearing on Psychiatric Care - Senator C. Harris and Governor Ann Richards, 116584 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Tissue Engineering Conference - Pheley, 2000; 116461 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Vision, 2001; 117454 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Wheel of Fortune, 116462 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Willy's birthday party, 116463 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Wine tasting - RMC (Spec's/Bear Dalton), 117469 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Subseries C: Students, faculty, staff, departments, groups, visitors, and speakers, 115521
    - Admissions stock, 116684 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Alumni portraits, 116561 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Alumni portraits, 116562 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Alumni portraits, 116563 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Art/Art History, 116568 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Baker 13, 116726 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Biochemistry stock, 116479 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Board of Governors/Trustees, 116480 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Board of Governors/Trustees, 116481 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Campanile Orchestra, 116482 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Campus Police, 116483 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Career Services, 117525 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Center for Religious Tolerance (Boniuk), 118757 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Center for the Study of Languages, 116484 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Computer Science - faculty photos, 116485 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Continuing Studies, 116486 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Debate Team, 116487 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Donor Honor Roll - Student Photos, 117526 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Dorms, 116488 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 118758 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Electrical Engineering, 116565 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Environmental Science and Engineering, 116566 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Environmental Science web pages, 2001; 116567 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Food and Dining Services, 116489 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - French and Italian Clubs, 116490 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Geology Boat, 116569 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - GSA, October 12, 1999; 116729 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Human Resources - staff portraits, 116491 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - KTRU, 116492 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Language Lab, 116570 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Lorenzo-Camacho Shadow Group, 117982 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Minority Affairs, 116493 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - MOB, 117386 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - NASA, 116494 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Navy/ROTC, 116495 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Owlmanac, 116496 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Physics faculty, 116685 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Presidents of the United States, 116497 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Physical Plant, 116498 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Portraits - Founder's Room and Hamman, 118759 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Registrar's Office, 117635 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Rice Dance Theater, 116499 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Rice Media Center, 116571 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Rice Media Center - exhibits, 116572 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Rice Players, 116500 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - The Rice School, 116501 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Rice Thresher, 116502 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Science stock, 116504 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Science stock, 116505 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Shepherd School of Music, 117490 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Spacce Science and Space Physics research, 118760 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Students, 116686 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Students - eating, 116506 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Students - games, 116507 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Students - in class, 117491 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Students - in class, 117492 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Students - moving in, 116508 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Students - music/art, 117586 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Students - recreation and leisure, 116509 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Students - sailing, 116510 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Students - studying, 117493 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Students - studying, 117494 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Students and faculty - recreation and leisure, 116511 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Visiting guests - Phil Gramm, Schmitt, External Affairs (Krista Tour), and Andre Watts, 116512 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - VROTC, 118065 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Watson winners, 117585 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Adams, David - Physics, 116679 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Akers, Bill and Nancy, 117589 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Albee, Edward, October 1986; 116519 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Alfven, Hannes, December 1974; 116520 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Allen, Herbert, 117444 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Aranda, Jose, 116600 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Ashworth, Kenneth H., 116585 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Askew, Rubin, December 1982; 116521 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Axson, Stockton, 117466 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Baker, Howard, April 1987; 116640 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Baker, Capt. James A., 117983 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Baker, James A., 117305 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Baker, Stephen, 117306 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Barnes, Tevia, 117307 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Barns, Joe, 118066 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Barrow, Andy, 118273 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Bayazitoglu, Yildiz, 117308 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Beatty, Anne, March 1986; 116522 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Beckwith, Boyd, 116601 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Berkman, Lance, 116523 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Berrera, Rick, 117390 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Bethe, Hans, 116524 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Birnbach, Lisa, November 1982; 116525 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Blaser, --, September 1981; 116526 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Bloch, Felix, January 1972; 116527 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Bok, Derek, October 1985; 116528 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Bolen, Kelly, 117471 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Boles, John, 116513 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Bond, Julian, November 1984; 116529 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Boney, Jew Don, 116530 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Bongmba, Elias, 117593 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Bonner, T.W., 117449 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Boothe, Nancy, 116602 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Braam, Janet, 117309 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Bradley, Alicia, 116748 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Bramlett, Linda, 116603 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Bray, Hubert, 117439 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Brewster, Kingman, 116531 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Briggs, Adaba, 117461 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Brock, Nathan, 116604 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Broker, Karin, 116746 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Brotzen, Franz, 117451 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Brown, George R., 116641 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Brown, Herman, 117980 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Brown, Judith, 117310 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Brown, Katherine Tsanoff, 116605 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Brown, Lee, 116587 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Brugger, Ernst, 116532 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Bryson, Barbara, 116606 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Burgess, Pat, 117311 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Burrus, Sid, 116514 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Burton, Richmond, 117312 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Butcher, E.D., 116607 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Byrd, Alex, 117313 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Caesar, Dan, 117463 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Caflisch, Anna, 116608 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Caldwell, 117442 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Camacho, Zenaido, 116609 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Cameron - portrait, 117434 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Carrere, Nelson, 117314 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Castaneda, Jim, 117315 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Chance, Jane, 117316 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - Chapman, Alan, 117317 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - Chappelear, 116559 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - Chisolm, Shirley (Hon.), 116642 (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - Christopher, Warren, 117318 (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Church, Geoffrey, 116610 (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Cohen, George and Esther - portraits, 117467 (Box 36, Folder 48)
    - Cohen, I Bernard, February 1983; 116533 (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - Colvin, Vicki, 117975 (Box 36, Folder 50)
    - Conrad, Will, 117504 (Box 36, Folder 51)
    - Cox, Ed, 116611 (Box 36, Folder 52)
    - Crawford, Sarah Nelson, 116612 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Creekmore, Howard, 117440 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Croneis, Cary, 117450 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Crowell, Steven, 116613 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Curall, Steve, 117319 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Curl, Bob, 117320 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Dalai Lama, 116534 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Daljarns, Alexander, April 1986; 116535 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Dallek, Robert, 116643 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Darnton, Robert C., 116644 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Davenport, Kimberly, 116737 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Davidson, Chandler, 117321 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Davies, Joseph I., 117452 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Davis, Mark, 117435 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - DeMenil, D, 116536 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Demopoulos, Demetrios, 117322 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Desilvio, Lorenzo, 117505 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Dickey, James, April 1986; 116537 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Dittman, Mark, 116614 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Djerassi, Carl, 1978; 116538 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Djerejian, Edward P., 117323 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Doerr, John, 117324 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Doody, Terry, 116691 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Drew, Katherine, 117468 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Dubay, Bren, 116615 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Dunning, Barry, 117397 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Dupont, Catherine, 117507 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Dyson, Freeman, March 1976; 116539 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Eliot, John, 118274 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Ellerbee, Linda, 116645 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Epstein, Marc, 117325 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Etnyre, Bruce, 117465 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Ette, Audrey, 117326 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Fischer, Norman, 117327 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Flores, Roland, 117542 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Franco, Eusebio, 116616 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Friedman, --, April 1984; 116540 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Fultz, Lucy, 117328 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Galbraith/Buckley, April 1986; 116541 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Gillis, Malcolm, 116515 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Gillis, Malcolm, 116703 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Gillis, Malcolm - North Carolina, 117329 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Gillis, Malcolm and Cindy Lindsay (trustee), 117594 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Gillis, Malcolm and Elizabeth Gillis, Bob McNair, and Janice McNair, 117393 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Gillis, Malcolm and Kenneth Pitzer, 117392 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Gillis, Malcolm and Wayne Graham, 117590 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Glass, Graham, 117976 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Gonzalez, Alessandra, 117510 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Gorbachev, Mikhail, 117330 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Graham, Billy, 116542 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Graham, Wayne, 117654 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Guanchez, Jennine, 117508 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Hackerman, Norman, 116617 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Haddad, Robert M., 117331 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Halas, Naomi, 116751 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Halberstram, 116543 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Hammond, Michael, 117470 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Harcombe, Paul A., 116618 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Harter, Deborah, 116619 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Haseltine, Jerome, 117462 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Haskell, Tom, 116690 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Hatfield, Ken, 117332 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Havens, Sandy, 117333 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Heath, Edward, April 1983; 116544 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Hebl, Mikki, 117334 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Heisman, John W., 117436 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Henderson, I.B., 116646 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Henderson, Roberta Kelley, 117335 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Henry, Charles, 117336 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Herring, Robert T., 117441 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Hickey, Damon, 116647 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Hicks, Marion, 116620 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Hirasaki, George, 117555 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Hirshberg, Alan, 116558 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Hoffman, Daniel, April 1984; 116545 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Houston, William V., 117430 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Howell, Judy, 116564 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Hoyle, Fred, May 1985; 116546 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Huffer, Lynn, 117337 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Hulet, R.G., 117338 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Hunter, John, 117556 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Huston, Dennis, 116747 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Hutchinson, John, 116621 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Huxley, Julian, 117432 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Iksander, Maryana, 116704 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Irwin, John, 116648 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Isle, Walter, 117339 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Johnson, David, 117340 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Johnson, Eric, 117341 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B, 1968-1969; 116547 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Jordan, Barbara, 1977; 116548 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Kaplan, Greg, 117342 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Kennedy, John F. (at Rice), 117981 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Kennedy, Ken, 116622 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - King, Roger, 117343 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Kinsey, Jim, 117655 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Kissinger, Henry, 116549 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Klineberg, Steven, 117344 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Konisky, Jordan, 117345 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Kraft, Christopher, January 9, 1979; 116649 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Kung, Hans, 116650 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Lane, Sarah, 116588 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Lanman, Dave, 116623 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Laux, Lila, 116624 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Leakey, Richard, 116651 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Leebron, David and Y. Ping Sun, 117388 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Lerup, Lars, 116516 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Letov, Alexander M, 116550 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Levy, Eugene, 116750 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Llope, Bill, 116680 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Llosa, Vargas, April 1986; 116589 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Loetscher, Hugo, 116652 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Long, Elizabeth, 116749 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Louie, Sylvia, 117346 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Lovejoy, Thomas, 116653 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - Lovett, Edgar Odell, 117984 (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - Lozano-Gonzales, Karen, 117347 (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - Mack, Bill, 116625 (Box 39, Folder 44)
    - Mailer, Norman, 116654 (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - Malherbe, Abraham J., 116655 (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - Margrave, John, 117974 (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - Martin, Bill, 117349 (Box 39, Folder 48)
    - Martin, Randi, 117350 (Box 39, Folder 49)
    - Martin, Ray, 116626 (Box 39, Folder 50)
    - Masterson, Peter, 116656 (Box 39, Folder 51)
    - Matherly, Cheryl, 116738 (Box 39, Folder 52)
    - Mathias, Sen. Charles, 116657 (Box 39, Folder 53)
    - Matthews, Kathy, 117351 (Box 39, Folder 54)
    - Matusow, Allen, 117352 (Box 39, Folder 55)
    - McCants, John Thomas, 117448 (Box 39, Folder 56)
    - McIntire, Larry, 117353 (Box 39, Folder 57)
    - McIntire, Mary, 117354 (Box 39, Folder 58)
    - McLeod, John and Kathy Alsop, 1975; 116658 (Box 39, Folder 59)
    - McMurtry, Burton, 117355 (Box 39, Folder 60)
    - McMurtry, Larry, 116705 (Box 39, Folder 61)
    - McReynolds, Walter, and Jeffery Geane, March 1984; 116678 (Box 39, Folder 62)
    - Mead, Andrew, 117973 (Box 39, Folder 63)
    - Michener, James, March 1984; 116551 (Box 39, Folder 64)
    - Miele, Angelo, 116590 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Mikos, Tony, 117592 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Milosz, Czeslaw and Ewa Thompson, 116706 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Minter, David, 117356 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Montague, Ashley, October 1986; 116552 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Moore, Barry, 116659 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Moore, Phil, 117506 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Morimoto, Colleen, 117464 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Morris, Bill, 117357 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Morris, Richard, 116660 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Murphy, Walter, 117358 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Naficy, Hamid, 116739 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Needham, Joseph, 116707 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Negroponte, John, 116661 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Nelson, Jack, 116662 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Nuremburg, David, 117395 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - O'Connor, Ralph, 117359 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - O'Connor, Sandra Day, February 14, 1986; 116586 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Oppenheimer, Danny, 117513 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Oster, Karen, 116743 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Padley, Paul, 116681 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Pais, Abraham, September 1985; 116663 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Parker, James A. (Hon.), 118294 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Parsons, Bill, 117360 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Pate, James L., 116664 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Patten, Robert, 117389 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Peierls, Sir Rudolf E., March 9, 1981; 116665 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Pfaff, Heather, 117472 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Pinn, Tony, 117361 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Pitman, Russ, 116560 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Pitzer, Kenneth, 116628 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Plattner, Ed, 116682 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Polking, John, 116741 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Press, Frank, 1979; 116553 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Price, Russell, 116708 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Prince Phillip, 1983; 116554 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Quillen, Carol, 116709 (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - Ramos, Suzanna and Bill Ciminelli, 116629 (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - Raven, Peter, February 1986; 116555 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Redgrave, Vanessa, February 1996; 116556 (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Reich, Robert, 116730 (Box 40, Folder 41)
    - Reiser, Adam, 1997; 116517 (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - Remington, Dave, 116666 (Box 40, Folder 43)
    - Rice, William Marsh, 116630 (Box 40, Folder 44)
    - Richter, George H., 117445 (Box 40, Folder 45)
    - Rickover, Hyman, 116667 (Box 40, Folder 46)
    - Ridilla, Marc, 117509 (Box 40, Folder 47)
    - Rixner, Scott, 117362 (Box 40, Folder 48)
    - Rosenblatt, Roger, 116668 (Box 40, Folder 49)
    - Rudolph, Fred, 117363 (Box 40, Folder 50)
    - Rupp, George, 116631 (Box 40, Folder 51)
    - Ryon, Lewis Babcock, 117443 (Box 40, Folder 52)
    - Sandved, Kjell, 116669 (Box 40, Folder 53)
    - Sass, Ron, 117364 (Box 40, Folder 54)
    - Sato, Hiroko, 117365 (Box 40, Folder 55)
    - Saxon, David S., 116670 (Box 40, Folder 56)
    - Scheid, Mark, 117366 (Box 40, Folder 57)
    - Schnietz, Karen, 117367 (Box 40, Folder 58)
    - Scuseria, Gustavo E., 116632 (Box 40, Folder 59)
    - Seaborg, 1982; 116727 (Box 40, Folder 60)
    - Seidelman, Angela with Paul Katz, 117368 (Box 40, Folder 61)
    - Seymour, Lynne, 116633 (Box 40, Folder 62)
    - Shapiro, Beth, 116634 (Box 40, Folder 63)
    - Sharon, Danielle, 117369 (Box 40, Folder 64)
    - Shatto, Gloria, 117438 (Box 40, Folder 65)
    - Shuck, Glenn W., 117370 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Smalley, Richard, 117371 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Smalley, Richard and Bob Curl, 117391 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Smith, George, 1981; 116557 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Smith, KA, 117372 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Rich, 116635 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Smith, Roland, 117373 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Sneider, Allison, 117374 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Sontag, Susan, 116671 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Spanos, Pol, 116744 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Spiegelman, Sol, 116672 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Stalkup, Fred, 116591 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Stein, Bob, 117375 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Stewart, Heather, 1997; 116518 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Stokes, Gale, 116745 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Stokes, Gale and Tony Gorry, 117394 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Stoppard, Tom, 116673 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Strassman, Joan, 117376 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Sullivan, Selby, 116674 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Talbott, Strobe, 116675 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Tapia, Richard, 116636 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Tarlov, Alvin R., 118761 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Taylor, Mathew, 116637 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Teller, Edward, April 12, 1982; 116676 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Thomas, The Rt. Hon. George, 116677 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Tour, Jim, 117377 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Tsanoff, Radoslav, 117433 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Unrau, Lia, 117378 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Urbish, Leona, 116638 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Valenzuela, Angela, 117396 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Vance, Cyrus, 117379 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Vandiver, Frank E., 117446 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Vardi, Moshe, 117380 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Vonnegut, Kurt, 117381 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Voswinkel, Mary, 116592 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Waggaman, Camille, 117431 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Watkin, William Ward, 117447 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Watts, Andre, 118633 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Weisner, Mark, 117382 (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - West, Jennifer, 116742 (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - Whitaker, Gil, 117383 (Box 41, Folder 41)
    - Whitmire, Ken, 117384 (Box 41, Folder 42)
    - Wihl, Gary, 117591 (Box 41, Folder 43)
    - Williams, Nikki L., 117541 (Box 41, Folder 44)
    - Wise, Scott, 116639 (Box 41, Folder 45)
    - Yaqub, Aaliya, 117511 (Box 41, Folder 46)
    - Yekovich, Robert, 117437 (Box 41, Folder 47)
    - Yepes, Pablo, 116683 (Box 41, Folder 48)
    - Young, Jim, 116740 (Box 41, Folder 49)
    - Zeff, Stephen A., 117385 (Box 41, Folder 50)
    - Zodrow, George, 117588 (Box 41, Folder 51)